Next, please answer what the
abbreviation is, not the meaning.
I got it.
NG.
What?
It means that I can't go that day.
I got it.
Oha!
Today, we have a lot of popular words
in the world.
Yes.
What is it?
Unazuki.
Unazuki?
Yes.
There are popular words, but there are
also words that have always been there.
What is the term that you usually hear?
I'm a celebrity.
I thought that there were many words
that you might not know just by mistake.
I'm not a celebrity.
I'm a celebrity.
I made a quiz for you.
This time, it's a personal battle.
It's always a personal battle.
No, it's not.
I'm a celebrity.
There are 15 questions in total.
There are a lot.
If the answers are the same,
Let's do rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
The first question.
What is the name of the person who is
crying now?
It's a familiar image.
The person who puts a number on the
stage and makes it easier to understand
the position of the person.
You are good at explaining.
I see.
You explained it in detail.
I wrote it in my dictionary.
The second question.
What is the name of the person who is
crying now?
Oh, I see.
I thought it was a male.
What? What?
Male?
It means that the time is getting
longer and longer.
It's like, I'm holding it.
There are a lot of them.
It means that the time is getting
longer.
I thought it was that.
I thought it was a seasoning.
I thought it was a female.
Oh, you thought it was a male?
Ah, that one!
I thought it was a male.
There are a lot of them.
Then, the third question.
What is this?
It's like a bounce.
That was Hazuki-san.
It means that it ends earlier than the
time we planned.
Then, the fourth question.
I learned this recently.
It means that it becomes like a
formation and becomes two rows.
It means that it opens one row and goes
down.
It's like a teleportation.
Officially, it's not just used like
that.
It doesn't mean that.
What?
I've only used it in dance.
In a way, it's like a formation.
That's the correct answer, but the
meaning is different.
So, should we be a little off the topic
of how we use it?
It's almost an answer, but let's do a
telepathy test.
Exchange.
It's telepathy.
I thought this was a good idea.
I told the girl in the dance club that
it's telepathy.
It's not a mistake.
It's a difference.
I didn't know that.
He is the one who is going to do the
rest.
Telecom is like changing the order.
I see.
It is used the most.
I learned a lot.
The fifth question.
Point.
Point?
Pen.
A stage set?
No.
Huh?
Oh, I see.
Yes.
A celebrity?
No.
A president?
A chairman?
No.
A peak?
Wait, a peak?
Hint!
Here's a quick example.
Yes.
Today's shoot is going to take a long
time, so it's going to end at the peak.
I see.
Sami-san.
12 o'clock.
That's right.
7 o'clock.
Yay!
I see.
That's right.
Basically, it's 12 o'clock at night.
Hmm.
That's right.
It's called the peak.
I knew it.
You knew?
If you get caught, you'll be like, oh.
I don't know that.
Then, the sixth question.
Chin.
I've heard it twice.
Fish.
Chin.
It's a fish soup.
Fish soup.
It's good.
It's a synonym.
Something that's popping out.
Egu.
We put it on the ground and it's egu.
6 o'clock.
I thought it was 6 o'clock.
I thought it was 6 o'clock because the
peak was at 12 o'clock.
It's a little difficult.
It's difficult.
Yes.
The hint for the quiz is.
I'm sorry if I get lost.
Do you get a chin in the shooting this
time?
Transportation fee.
That's good.
It's a good feeling.
I've been looking at it.
I don't lose.
I'm close.
Dinner.
Drink.
Rice table.
What? It's rice.
It's a food.
I didn't know that.
Let's use this.
I'll use this.
I'm sure that Captain will be angry.
I'm sure.
I'll use this.
Are you sure?
Please subscribe to this channel.
I think you all know the 7th question.
What is the name of the city where the
first train was built?
Kotsuhi
I've heard of it.
The 8th question.
What is the name of the city where the
first train was built?
Keihi
It's a little rough.
I have a hint.
The answer is...
Do you often get a massage on your chin
and feet?
Kotsuhi
Hikuhaku-hi
Correct!
Please subscribe to this channel!
Yaaaaaaaaay!!
Question 9
Please answer what the abbreviation is,
not the meaning.
I got it.
NG
It means that I can't go on that day.
I thought it was an abbreviation of NG.
I see.
Not whole
Not good
I said it wrong.
What kind of word is NG?
No
But if you use the word, it's English.
Not guy
I got it.
Not good
I said it wrong.
It means no good.
It's almost correct.
I got it.
I was scared.
Question 10
Please answer what the abbreviation is,
not the meaning.
I got it.
Master Ceremony
You are close.
You are almost right.
Master Celebration
You are close to the answer.
You are almost right.
Mustard Ceremony
Master of Ceremony
Wow!
You are serious to MC.
I am serious.
Question 11
Gumi-kuro
Rehearsal
Question 12
I was about to do it, but I was wrong.
Mr.Folk
I knew it.
You are good at using the abbreviation.
Question 12
Warai
My gag is funny.
You are good at it.
Waraigoe
Warao Amu
You are funny.
This is difficult.
Please laugh at the chair next to you.
Yokete
You are laughing so that you can't be
filmed.
I see.
I've never heard of it.
You are always saying like this.
I've never said it on TV.
I think you are laughing.
You should be careful not to laugh at
such a moment.
You are laughing.
You are funny.
Question 13
Waraimu
I go to the location before that day.
I love Minorin.
Minorin is easy.
It's really easy.
Question 14.
Shoot.
Shoot?
To score a goal.
It's a very rough hint, but you're
shooting now.
Shooting?
What?
Is that shooting?
Shooting is shooting.
I see.
It's shooting in English.
Damn it.
I can't think of it in Japanese.
Shooting is a word for a comedian.
I'm frustrated.
This is the last question.
Question 15.
You can get the wrong answer.
What?
Answer is...
A show.
A ride.
A car.
A car?
What?
A wife's love sign event
Cute
Cute love event
But the first answer of Takazuki-san
and Fujisaki-san is not clear
It's coming from there
Love sign event
Driving together
That's the program
Men and women driving together
Driving together
Let's ride together
Two people riding together
A driver who I was interested in at the
bus stop
I got a ride and got married
A driver who I was interested in at the
bus stop
I got a ride and got married
As an example, everyone has a live
tomorrow, but I prepared a schedule for
a sudden bundle
Ah, double booking for work
Ah, a little
A little
After work
Oh, great
If you say something very roughly,
another schedule will be on the day when
the original schedule is included.
It's me today
Today this is included, so showroom
delivery
That's a love song
Love song
Oh, good
I like it
Love song
Yes, this is the end
It was difficult
The collection is over
There are two winners
I'm white again
Great confidence
The second industry requirement is
Kitani and
Yay
You?
I lost
Eh
So if you have an industry requirement
you don't know, you can ask these two
Certainly
I understand anything
Thank you
Please
Strawberry Seika
Early
It was early
Please tell me the industry
requirements you know
Please tell me
Food industry
Oh, good
Yes
Goodbye
Bye Bye